Hello friends, welcome to our YouTube channel.
Friends, in today's video
we will talk
about the advisor job in ICICI PDL Life Insurance.
Friends, there are two types of jobs here.
One is your employee and the other
is your advisor.  According to me, it is
better if the employees do not join the company.
But if you want to work professionally
then you can join an employee
because in an employee you
get a fixed salary and you definitely get work
pressure and targets here.
That is why friends,
I will talk to you about today's topic in Advisor Advisor.
If you are sitting free at home and there is
no one to put work pressure on you.  If you keep earning a
good amount of money then you should
definitely join an advisor.  Ok?  So
what information should I tell you in this?   Let me
tell you how to join it
, how to work,
what are the methods to work and join.  Ok
?  What exams have to be given for this
, we will tell you everything in detail here.
But before moving ahead, I
request you that if you have not subscribed to our channel
yet, then
subscribe today itself.  Also press the bell icon
so that all the upcoming
job notifications reach you first.
Friends, after coming to this page, you will have to
directly click on it and
here we will tell you all the information step by step.
First of all, let me tell you
friends that
if you do advisor job in Advisor i.e. IC Prudential, then
here you do not have any boss over you.
Here you are the boss and
friends, you
can generate a good income here.  Yes, there is
no fixed salary in advisor.
But the commission you will get is very
high, it is more than the salary
you get here.  And friends, the commission is not like that if
you close a file,
its commission comes after 3 days, 4 days or 1 month, it is not like that.  If
you close the file
one day, then on the same day you will get
the commission in your account.  Apart from this,
friends, if you do good work then you are
globally recognized here.
Like there are tours in Goa or
Dubai, whatever you have is taken there also.
Apart from this,
friends, you
also get expert training here.  Support is also available.
You get support here any time,
which is a great thing.  If we talk about the
present time, then
friends, more than 2 lakh advisors are
working in ICICI PIL and those who are
earning more than six lakhs, there are
advisors here who are earning Rs 6 lakhs or even more per month.
Okay, and let me tell you
that the products here,
all the products in the market, are
competitive products here.  So
you will not face any inconvenience in selling the product here.
Apart from this, friends, if you do
good work then
you also get to visit more than 40 countries,
which the company bears, all the amounts,
friends, here I am telling you that
ICICI Pall has an edge app through which
you can easily close the customer's file,
if I
tell you who can join here, then be it a woman
or a working professional or a
youth or a retired professional or a
financial professional, every type of
candidate can apply here, let
me also tell you the details of how to apply.
But its IC's I
Proof Edge or application, you can
generate everything in that one application.
You can generate everything here, from new business to closing the business.  You
can also monitor your commission here.  Ok?  Friends, let us now talk about
who can join here.
So, as I have already
told you about joining, whether you are a woman or a
retired employee or a professional
youth or a working professional, you can join here,
but whatever age
criteria etc. are there for that, I will tell you all of that here.
What will happen is that your age should be
18 years or more.
Apart from this, if the qualification you have is
12th pass or more, it will also be fine.
Ok?  Must have minimum 12th pass.
12th pass: For this, in the area where the
population is 5000 or more,
12th pass has been made mandatory for that area.
But if your area is
rural and the population is
less than 5000, then your qualification will be
10th pass.  Ok?  And
tell me what will be your role as an
advisor here?  So what will be the role that
whatever leads will be generated,
you will have to follow those leads thoroughly
and generate business through them.
Simply put, the
more customers you can get insured,
the more commission you will get here.  To
join here you will have to
follow simply five steps.  First of all
you will have to fill the form.
After that, as soon as you submit the document,
it will be verified.  After the verification is complete, the
IRDI
exam will be conducted for you.  Friends, this is from
IRDI i.e. Insurance Regulatory
and Development Authority of India.   It
is necessary to get this insurance certificate.
No, otherwise you will
not be able to sell insurance other than this.  So as soon as you complete the
exam, you will
also have to appear for an internal exam from the ICC.
After passing that, you will be given
an appointment letter from ICC.  That means
you can work independently as an advisor.  Ok.
How to apply for it now?  So for that,
first of all, in the links that were coming in front of you,
here you should give your full name,
mobile number, email ID and the mobile number on
which WhatsApp is available.  After that
mention your gender and then your occupation here whether you are a government servant,
private servant, doctor,
insurance agent or you are retired or a
student.  After mentioning all this,
mention your pin code number here.
After that submit.  So,
you will get a reply from ICC Productions
within one, two or three days.
After that you
can join.  Friends, remember one thing
that there are no
fees, charges etc. for joining here.  You can easily join here free of cost and
live a good life.
So friends, that's all for now in the video.
If you like the video, please like, share and
subscribe.  Thank you.